I have a real estate law firm.
We do 2.5 million.
What's the bottom line?
About 500.
I also myself operate a marketing company.
My wife operates the law firm.
OK.
How much does the agency make?
450 top line, 200 EBITDA.
So do you not want to full time market into your wife's law firm?
It's tough to stop something that's making $200,000 in my pocket every year.
How much time do you put towards the agency?
30 to 35 hours a week.
If you took 30 to 35 hours a week and put it towards the thing that's already making,
you know, seven times as much money, do you think you'd be able to find a way to get the extra 200?
I guess my problem is like how to shut something down like the right way, I guess.
Yeah, no, it's a great question.
I'd say, listen, you know, it's been an amazing time.
You guys have been loyal clients.
I just want to let you know two things.
Number one is we stopped accepting new customers.
And number two, we're going to be basically phasing this out over the next six months.
And so I wanted to give you guys six months.
We will continue levels of service for this period of time.
Also, I have three recommendations of people who I trust in this industry.
I think will do a good job.
And then you negotiate deals with those guys to give you kickbacks for all this book of business.
And you'll probably be able to make 100 grand a year just from referring the business out to those guys,
which they'll happily do.